aconvert.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy policy - Aconvert.com

**Latest privacy update (April 15, 2019): Added Cookie Consent Kit to all pages; files can be deleted immediately without waiting 2 hours.**

Aconvert.com is dedicated to making your online experience as interesting and enjoyable as possible. We truly appreciate your presence on our site and at all times understand that you are our guest and should be treated accordingly. To ensure this, we have listed the components of our Privacy Policy below. This Privacy Policy lets you know what happens to any personal data that you give to us or that we collect from you. We collect only the minimum amount of personal information necessary for you to make use of our services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third party applications or software that integrate with the services, or any other third party products, services or businesses, where we are not the controller of your personal data. 

If you have any questions regarding the processing of your personal data, as well as your rights regarding data privacy, please contact: support@aconvert.com.

#### Information about Google services

On our website we use several services of Google LLC ("Google"), 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.

More detailed information about the specific Google services we use on our website can be found following in this privacy policy.

By integrating Google services, Google may collect and process information (including personal data) about you. It cannot be excluded that Google may also transfer the information to a server in a third country.

As stated in Google's Privacy Shield certification (you can find it under <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list> by searching for "Google"), Google committed to comply to the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework for the collection, usage, and storage of personal data from EU or Swiss member states. Google, including Google LLC and its wholly-owned subsidiaries in the USA, has stated via certification to comply to the Privacy Shield principles. Further information can be found at <https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks?gl=en>.

We ourselves cannot influence which data is collected and processed by Google. However, Google states that, among others, the following information (including personal data) might be processed:

  * Protocol data (especially the IP address)
  * Location-related information
  * Unique application numbers
  * Cookies and similar technologies

Information about the types of cookies Google uses can be found at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/types>.

If you are signed in using your Google account, Google may add the processed information to your account and treat it like personal data, depending on your account settings. To do so, Google does, among others, the following:

_"When you're not signed in to a Google Account, we store the information we collect with unique identifiers tied to the browser, application, or device you're using. This helps us do things like maintain your language preferences across browsing sessions. When you're signed in, we also collect information that we store with your Google Account, which we treat as personal information."_ (<https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>)

A direct addition of this data can be prevented by logging out of your Google account or by adjusting the appropriate account settings in your Google account. Furthermore, you can prevent the installation of cookies – if Google sets them – by using the appropriate settings in your browser; however we would like to point out that, in this case, you may not be able to use all functions of this website to their full extent.

Further information can be found in Google's privacy policy, which can be found here: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

Information about Google's privacy settings can be found at <https://privacy.google.com/take-control.html>.

#### Use of cookies

To make this site work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too.

**What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don't have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. 

**How do we use cookies?**

Aconvert.com does not use any first-party cookies require consent. Our website uses third party services such as advertising from Google Adsense that may use cookies. 

**Google Adsense cookies**

On our website, we use the functions of the online advertising service Google AdSense. Google AdSense is a service of Google Inc. ("Google"), 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google AdSense is a Google service that displays Google advertisements from advertisers on third-party websites. By integrating Google AdSense we provide Google with appropriate advertising space on our website.

Google AdSense uses so-called "cookies", which are text files that are saved on your device and that enabled the website to conduct an analysis of the websites you visited. Google AdSense may also use so-called web beacons (invisible graphics). Via these web beacons, information such as the visitor traffic on the pages of this offer can be evaluated. The information generated by cookies and web beacons about the usage of our website (including your IP address) and the delivery of advertising formats will be transmitted to and stored by a Google server that might be located in the USA or other third countries. This way, Google can reconstruct on which websites the usage of advertising media took place in order to be able to allocate a commission to the website operator.

The following information (including personal data) might be processed:

  * Your web request
  * Your IP address
  * Your browser type
  * Your browser language
  * The date and time of your request
  * One or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser

You have the right to object. To do so, you can prevent the acquisition of the data generated by the cookies (including your IP address) by Google as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>

In addition, you have the possibility to deactivate the interest-based ads from Google according to the instructions in the following link: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>

More information about Google Adsense's privacy: [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/), [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout).

**DoubleClick cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting").

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

**Opting out of ads personalization**

You can opt out of ads personalization by using Google's Ads Settings (<https://www.google.com/settings/ads>). If you opt out of ads personalization, you will no longer receive personalized advertising from Google.

Personalized ads reach users based on their interests, demographics, and other criteria. Ad technology providers may collect, receive, and use personal data from users in personalized ads, you can find all ad technology providers at [ https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/9012903](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/9012903).

Non-personalized ads are targeted using contextual information rather than the past behavior of a user. Although these ads don't use cookies for ads personalization, they do use cookies to allow for frequency capping, aggregated ad reporting, and to combat fraud and abuse.

**How to control cookies?**

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see [aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work.

**Right of objection**

You have the right to object.

In your browser settings you can restrict or completely prevent the use of cookies. You can also prompt the automatic deletion of cookies when a browser window is closed.

You can find out how to delete and change the cookie settings of the most common browsers here:

  * Google Chrome: [Website](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)
  * Mozilla Firefox: [Website](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored)
  * Apple Safari: [Website](https://support.apple.com/en-euro/guide/safari/sfri11471/mac)
  * Microsoft Internet Explorer: [Website](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies)

#### Data protection

**Personal information**

When visiting Aconvert.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Aconvert.com doesn't require registration to use. That means we DO NOT collect your name, email address, company name or password etc.

Aconvert.com will never share your personal information with any Third Party business organization that intends to use it for direct marketing purposes unless you have given us specific permission to do so. The processed information will only be stored as long as it is necessary for the purpose it was processed for or for as long as it is legally required.

**Storage of files**

All the files uploaded for processing on Aconvert.com are stored on an appropriate server located at North America or Europe for processing and the download afterwards. All user-uploaded files as well as the converted output files will be deleted in two hours after upload or conversion respectively. We keep the files for the sole purpose of giving you enough time to download them. During that time, we don't look at the files or mine any data from them. No backups are made of any uploaded files nor their processed output neither are the contents monitored without the explicit permission of user. We do not claim ownership in any of your files that you upload.

**Data security**

All filenames are generated randomly and cannot be guessed. All communications between your web browser and the conversion servers are through secure channel with HTTPS enabled, which prevents data to be altered or diverted. This completely protects your data from unauthorized access. All collected information on the website is protected from disclosure and unauthorized access by using physical, electronic and managerial protection procedures. 

**Right of objection**

We allow you to access, modify, or delete the personal data collected by us. If you would like to do so, please contact us at support@aconvert.com. We will get back to you as soon as possible.

Please note that uploaded and processed files are never stored longer than two hours on our servers and are then deleted permanently. During this hour, your files are not accessed, copied, analyzed or anything else unless you provide us with the explicit written permission to do so. You can instantly delete your files without waiting. To do so, click the download icon next to your file, then click "Delete File" button. This implies that you can delete your files on your own anytime. We can't make a backup copy of your files even if you ask us to do so.

#### Apps for Android

Aconvert.com built apps as Ad Supported apps. This SERVICE is provided by Aconvert.com at no cost and is intended for use as is. For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that we request will be retained on your device and is not collected by us in any way.

Our JPG to PDF Converter app uses permissions that are associated with accessing camera. This permission allows this application to capture images in order to be converted to a PDF file within this application. This permission can be rejected. Our online file conversion services may require you to upload files to convert. Your files will be for only you to access and will be automatically removed permanently on our server in 2 hours.

Our apps use third party services that may collect information used to identify you. Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by our apps:

**AdMob**

AdMob, is Google's mobile app advertising platform designed specifically for app developers. In order to understand Google's use of Data, consult Google's partner policy.

The following information (including personal data) might be processed:

  * Online identifiers, including cookie identifiers
  * IP addresses
  * Device identifiers
  * Client identifiers 
  * Unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example)
  * Usage Data.

Retention:

Google anonymizes the log data by removing part of the IP address (after 9 months) and cookie information (after 18 months)

More information about Google Admob's privacy: [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/), [Opt out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), [Service Information](https://privacy.google.com/businesses/adsservices/), [Partner policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites), [Ad technology providers](https://support.google.com/admob/answer/9012903).

**Google Play Services**

Google Play Services offers APIs and security services to the Android developer ecosystem. Google acts as a data controller for any personal data processed in Google Play Services, and offers user notices and consents about the use of personal data in the service's user interface in Android.

The following information (including personal data) might be processed:

  * Device information
  * Log information
  * Location information
  * Unique application numbers
  * Local storage
  * Cookies and similar technologies

Google use the collected information to provide, maintain, protect and improve Google's services, to develop new ones, and to protect Google and the users. Google also use this information to offer you tailored content – like giving you more relevant search results and ads.

More information about Google Play Services's privacy: [Google Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms), [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

**Distribution**

The only official channel for distribution of our apps for Android is Google Play Store. Any other mode of distribution is not official and thus, is not maintained by the developer. This privacy policy is effective to distribution made on official channel only.

#### Third party websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Google Drive**

Google Drive is a service provided by Google LLC, located at 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View California 94043, USA. If you're based in the European Economic Area or Switzerland, Google Drive is provided by Google Ireland Limited, a company incorporated and operating under the laws of Ireland (Registered Number:368047), and located at Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland. The [Google Drive Terms of Service](https://www.google.com/drive/terms-of-service/) cover your use of and access to Google Drive and your content in Google Drive. The [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) explains how Google collect and use your information while Google [Program Policies](https://support.google.com/docs/answer/148505?hl=en) outline your responsibilities when using the Service.

**Dropbox**

The [Terms of Service](https://www.dropbox.com/privacy#terms) of Dropbox cover your use and access to their services, client software and websites ("Services"). If you reside outside of the United States of America, Canada and Mexico ("North America") your agreement is with Dropbox International Unlimited Company, and if you reside in North America your agreement is with Dropbox, Inc. [Privacy Policy](https://www.dropbox.com/privacy2018) of Dropbox explains how they collect and use your information while their [Acceptable Use Policy](https://www.dropbox.com/terms#acceptable_use) outlines your responsibilities when using their Services. By using their Services, you're agreeing to be bound by Terms of Service, [Privacy Policy](https://www.dropbox.com/privacy2018), and [Acceptable Use Policy](https://www.dropbox.com/terms#acceptable_use).

**Payment via PayPal**

You have the possibility to pay via PayPal. Upon completion of your order, you will be redirected to the website of the payment provider PayPal (Europe) S.à r.l. et Cie, S.C.A., 22-24 Boulevard Royal, L-2449 Luxembourg („PayPal"). When paying via PayPal, information (including personal data) is transferred from us to PayPal and processed by PayPal for the purpose of payment processing. When paying via PayPal, the following data is transferred to PayPal in particular:

  * Price
  * Name of the product
  * Unique user ID (whole number)

When accessing the PayPal website or services of PayPal, PayPal sets cookies on your device. PayPal uses these cookies, among others, to identify you as a customer, to personalize PayPal services, contents, and ads, as well as to evaluate the effectiveness of advertisement, and to ensure the security of your account. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser, provided that these cookies aren't used to prevent fraud or to ensure the security of websites managed by PayPal. However, we would like to point out that in this case you may not be able to use all functions of PayPal to the full extent. 

You can view PayPal's current privacy policy here: <https://www.paypal.com/ie/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full?locale.x=en_IE>

As part of the transaction, we receive the following data from PayPal: <https://developer.paypal.com/docs/classic/ipn/integration-guide/IPNIntro/#ipn-protocol-and-architecture> The purpose of the data processing is the processing of the payment process and the contract.

The legal basis for the processing of personal data in the payment process and the processing of the contract is art. 6 para. 1 lit. b) DSGVO. For this, the data is stored only as long as it is necessary for the implementation and processing of your order and the fulfillment of legal storage periods.

The provision of personal data is required for the conclusion of a contract. The lack of provision results in the contract not being able to be concluded. 

#### Contact

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy and GDPR compliance, feel free to contact us at:  
Jimmy Liu   
Rm208,3 building, No.72 YinSan  
Shanghai 200136, China  
Email: support@aconvert.com.
